Guide to the English Department records, 1895-2006 RG0070
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Jenny McKean Moore Fund for Writers records, 1978-2006; RG0070 Series 3; 3 Linear feet
  - JMMF - National Museum of Women in the Arts, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - JMMF - T/X Progress, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - JMMF Cave Canem, 1998-2000 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - JMMF African American Writers Guild, 1994-1997 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Jenny Moore Fund, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Jenny Moore Fund - GWU English Dept, 1994-1998 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - JMMF - Turkey Thicket, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - JMMF - Joy Jones/Turkey Thicket Ref Center, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Writers Corps, 1998-2000 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Checks Stubs, 1998-2000 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Resolution No. 1, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Resolution No. 2, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Distance Education course recordings, 02/28/2005-05/25/2005; Series 4; 0.05 Linear Feet 1 document box
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains CDs and DVDs for two online courses SDLI Creative Writing and Engl 092 Post Colonial Literature II. The creative writing coures was taught by Professor David McAleavey. He interviewed faculty from the English Department about their creative writing process. He used these interviews for instruction. The Engl 092 Post Colonial Literature II was taught by Dr. Davita Daiya as part of the 2005 Distance Education Series produced by Academic Technologies. All of these cds were recorded in 2005.
  - SDLI Creative Writing Poetry course, 02/28/2005; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - SDLI Creative Writing course interview Vikram Chandra, 02/28/2005-05/23/2005; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    There is one CD and one DVD in this file. The one dated 05/23/2005 is the CD and indicates it has been edited.
  - SDLI Creative Writing course interview and poetry lecture with Jane Shore, 03/11/2005-05/18/2005; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    There is one CD and one DVD in this file. The one dated 05/18/2005 is the CD and it indicates it has been edited.
  - SDLI Creative Writing course introduction first draft, 3/21/2005; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - SDLI Creative Writing course Pati Griffith Rushes and interview, 3/29/2005-05/25/2005; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    This folder containes two CDs. The one dated 03/29/2005 has the title Rushes and the one dated 05/25/2005 indicates it has been edited.
  - SDLI Creative Writing course Anna Zeigler interview, 04/01/2005-05/25/2005; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    This folder containes two CDs. The one dated 04/01/2005 says rough cuts and the one dated 05/25/2005 indicates it has been edited.
  - SDLI Creative Writing course Maxine Clair interview, 04/06/2005-05/23/2005; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    This folder contains two CDs. The one dated 04/06/2005 says rough cuts and the one dated 05/23/2005 indicates it has been edited.
  - SDLI Creative Writing course Faye Moskowitz rough cut, 04/06/2005; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - SDLI Creative Writing course experimental writing forum, 05/11/2005-05/25/2005; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    This folder contains one CD and one DVD. The CD is dated 05/25/2005 says that it has been edited.
  - Engl 092 Post Colonial Literature II classes #5 and #10, 2005; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    Class #5 is Dr. Kavita Daiya with special guest Witi Ihimaera. Class #10 is Dr. Kavita Daiya with guest Bernadine Evaristo.